<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Entrepreneur Development</string>

    <string name="self">Information:-\n
        Self-Help Group (SHG) awareness promotes grassroots organizations that unite
        individuals for mutual support and development. These groups focus on economic
        empowerment through collective savings and credit activities, fostering social
        cohesion. Awareness initiatives highlight benefits like financial inclusion and skill
        development, acknowledging challenges. Success stories showcase improved
        livelihoods. Government and NGO support contribute to sustainability.
        SHG awareness is crucial for fostering resilient and empowered communities. </string>

    <string name="woman">Information:-\n
        Women empowerment is a comprehensive concept encompassing social, economic, and
        political dimensions. It involves breaking down gender-based barriers, providing
        opportunities, and enabling women to participate fully in all aspects of life.
        Key aspects include access to education, healthcare, and economic resources, along
        with equal opportunities in the workplace. Empowerment also entails promoting women
        involvement in decision-making and challenging stereotypes. By fostering women empowerment,
        societies can unlock the potential of their female population, leading to greater social equity,
        economic development, and overall progress. It is both a matter of justice and a strategic
        imperative for building a more inclusive and sustainable world.
        </string>

    <string name="ltg">Information:-\n
        Local to Global encapsulates the process of entities, initiatives, or ideas expanding
        from a local to a global scale. In business, companies often start locally before entering
        global markets, requiring strategic adaptations. Similarly, technological advancements
        and social shifts involve integrating global perspectives. The trajectory from local to
        global signifies evolution, collaboration, and adaptation across various sectors,
        emphasizing the interconnectedness of the world and the need for holistic approaches
        to address global challenges.
        </string>

    <string name="per">Information:-\n
        Personality development is a lifelong process involving the refinement of traits,
        behaviors, and emotional patterns. Influenced by genetics, environment, and
        experiences, it is crucial for holistic growth. Interactions in familial, cultural,
        and societal spheres, along with education, shape social, emotional, and intellectual
        aspects. Self-awareness is key for informed decision-making. Emotional intelligence
        and coping skills contribute to mental well-being. Goal setting and commitment to
        values guide development. It\'s a dynamic process requiring continuous self-reflection,
        adaptability, and an open-minded approach, leading to a well-rounded and evolving
        individual throughout life.
    </string>

    <string name="fap">Information:-\
        Finance and planning, integral for resource management in business and personal
        contexts, involve judicious use of money and strategic goal-setting. In businesses,
        financial planning forecasts needs, optimizes performance, and aligns with strategic
        goals. The collaboration ensures harmony between financial objectives and
        organizational vision, facilitating effective decision-making. In personal finance,
        planning includes budgeting, saving, and investing for stability. This dynamic
        relationship is crucial for navigating complexities in both business and personal
        landscapes, providing a structured approach for realizing aspirations and maintaining
        financial well-being.
        </string>

    <string name="candle">Information:-\n
        Candle making blends creativity with practicality, shaping wax into beautiful sources of
        light. Enthusiasts use various wax types, colors, scents, and molds for diverse designs.
        The process involves melting wax, adding dyes and fragrances, and pouring into molds. From
        traditional to intricate creations, candle making offers endless possibilities. Many enjoy
        it as a hobby, while entrepreneurs turn it into a business, offering unique, handmade candles
        appreciated for their personal touch. Beyond art, it\'s a therapeutic experience, yielding
        functional and aesthetically pleasing products. Whether for personal use or sale, handmade
        candles add warmth and ambiance to any setting.
        </string>

    <string name="dm">Information:-\n
        Digital marketing is a dynamic approach using online channels to engage a target
        audience. Key elements include SEO for improved search visibility, content marketing
        for creating valuable content, social media for direct interaction, and email marketing
        for personalized communication. Digital advertising, including display, PPC, and social
        media ads, widens reach and allows for performance tracking. The data-driven nature
        of digital marketing provides real-time insights for continuous improvement, making it
        an indispensable strategy for businesses in today\'s digital age.
        </string>

    <string name="soap">Information:-\n
        Soap making blends science and creativity, involving the chemical process of
        saponification where oils and an alkaline solution create soap and glycerin. Crafters
        choose oils, fragrances, and additives to customize characteristics like scent and
        texture. From traditional bars to innovative shapes and colors, soap making offers
        endless possibilities. Enthusiasts experiment with unique ingredients and techniques,
        embracing it as a fulfilling hobby or small business. The craft\'s popularity stems from
        personalized touches, natural ingredients, and environmental sustainability, resonating
        with consumers seeking artisanal products.
        </string>
    <string name="iae">Information:-\n
        Import and export are vital components of international trade, enabling the exchange
        of goods and services between countries. Import involves buying foreign products,
        broadening domestic market options, and accessing resources. Export entails selling
        domestically produced goods abroad, fostering economic growth. The balance
        between imports and exports influences a country\'s trade balance and economic
        stability. Governed by trade policies and regulations, these activities promote
        international cooperation, economic development, and cultural exchange. Effectively
        managing import and export enhances a nation\'s economic competitiveness and
        global integration.
        </string>
    <string name="paper">Information:-\n
        Paper bag making is a sustainable craft using recyclable and biodegradable materials
        to create eco-friendly alternatives to plastic bags. The process involves cutting,
        folding, and gluing paper to produce sturdy bags of various shapes and sizes.
        Entrepreneurs and artisans often turn this craft into a small-scale business, offering
        personalized designs. Beyond economic potential, paper bag making aligns with
        global efforts for environmentally responsible practices, addressing the issue of
        single-use plastic bags. With increasing consumer demand for sustainable options,
        paper bag making blends functionality with ecological consciousness, promoting a
        greener and more responsible approach to packaging and everyday carry.
        </string>

    <string name="ent">
        Information:-\n
        Entrepreneur Awareness Programme provides knowledge and skills for business
        ventures, covering ideation, market research, financial planning, and risk management.
        The initiative includes workshops, seminars, mentorship, and practical exercises to
        encourage innovation and economic growth. Enhancing awareness and competencies
        contributes to a dynamic business ecosystem, fostering resilience and empowering
        participants. The program also offers insights into industry trends and networking
        opportunities.
        </string>

    <string name="spices">Information:-\n
        Spice making is an ancient craft involving the skillful blending and processing of herbs
        and spices to create aromatic mixtures that enhance the richness of dishes. The
        process starts with sourcing high-quality raw spices, which are carefully measured and
        ground to unlock their unique flavors. Skilled spice makers create proprietary blends,
        combining spices in precise ratios to craft signature seasoning mixes. This art not only
        adds depth to cuisines but also allows for the creation of diverse and culturally
        significant flavor profiles. From traditional spice markets to modern kitchens, spice
        making plays a vital role in elevating the culinary experience and connecting people to
        a global tapestry of flavors.
        </string>

    <string name="palm">Information:-\n
        Palm leaf article making is a traditional craft where artisans skillfully transform palm
        leaves into practical and artistic items like baskets, mats, and hats. The process
        involves harvesting, drying, and softening mature palm leaves, followed by weaving
        using traditional techniques passed down through generations. These creations serve
        both practical and eco-friendly purposes, offering alternatives to modern materials,
        while also reflecting the cultural heritage of the communities practicing this craft. Palm
        leaf article making showcases resourcefulness, preserves traditional craftsmanship,
        and provides insight into the artistry and cultural identity of those involved in this
        age-old practice.
        </string>

    <string name="perfume">Information:-\n
        Perfume making is an artful process that involves blending essential oils, aromatic
        compounds, and fixatives to create unique scents. Perfumers, or "noses," select and
        combine fragrance notes to achieve harmonious profiles, including top, middle, and
        base notes. Essential oils are extracted from botanical sources and skillfully blended in
        precise ratios to craft the desired fragrance. Fixatives are added for longevity. This
        intersection of science and art allows individuals to express individuality through
        olfactory experiences, with the industry offering a diverse range of classic, niche,
        and custom blends. Perfume making is a dynamic realm of sensory artistry beyond
        personal grooming.
        </string>

    <string name="chocolate">
        Information:-\n
        Chocolate making is a delightful culinary craft involving transforming cocoa beans into
        treats. The process includes harvesting, fermenting, roasting, and grinding cocoa
        beans to produce cocoa mass. Skilled chocolatiers temper the chocolate for texture,
        gloss, and snap. Ingredients like sugar, milk, and flavors are added, and melted
        chocolate is molded into various shapes before controlled cooling. Experimentation
        results in a range of flavors and textures, from classic milk chocolate to rich dark
        varieties. Chocolate making, an art that brings worldwide joy, combines tradition and
        innovation to produce tempting confections.
        </string>

    <string name="screen1">Sign in or\n Register</string>
    <string name="screen2">Choose Courses</string>
    <string name="screen3">Easy Booking</string>
    <string name="screen1desc"> Access your account or create a new one to get started.</string>
    <string name="screen2desc">Browse through available courses and select the one that suits your interests or needs.</string>
    <string name="screen3desc"> Streamlined process for reserving your spot in the selected course with minimal hassle.</string>
    <string name="startDesc">Discover an extensive selection of courses covering various subjects and disciplines to meet your learning needs and preferences.</string>

    <string name="selftime">Date:- 22/05/2024, Time:-6:00 PM,\n Duration:- 1 hrs, Trainer Name:- Aryan Tambe</string>
    <string name="LTGtime"> Date :- 23/05/2024, Time:-4:00 PM,\n Duration:- 3 hrs, Trainer Name:- Chirag Choudhari</string>
    <string name="womentime">Date :- 21/05/2024, Time:-5:00 PM,\n Duration:- 2 hrs, Trainer Name:- Pratik Maske</string>
    <string name="Personalitytime"> Date :- 24/05/2024, Time:-3:00 PM,\n Duration:- 2 hrs, Trainer Name:- Chaitanya Bhat</string>
    <string name="Financetime">Date :- 26/05/2024, Time:-2:00 PM,\n Duration:- 1 hrs, Trainer Name:- Soham Parab</string>

    <string name="Digitime">Date :- 23/05/2024, Time:-5:00 PM,\n Duration:- 2 days, Trainer Name:- Pratik Maske</string>
    <string name="Soaptime">Date :– 22/05/2024, Time:-6:00 PM,\n Duration:- 1-2 days, Trainer Name:- Aryan Tambe</string>
    <string name="IAEtime"> Date :- 24/05/2024, Time:-4:00 PM,\n Duration:- 2 days, Trainer Name:- Soham Parab</string>
    <string name="Papertime">Date:- 22/05/2024, Time:-6:00 PM,\n Duration:- 1 days, Trainer Name:- Aryan Tambe</string>
    <string name="Entretime"> Date :- 27/05/2024, Time:-6:00 PM,\n Duration:- 1 days, Trainer Name:- Soham Parab</string>

    <string name="Candletime">Date :- 27/5/2024, Time:-1:00 PM,\n Duration:- 1 week, Trainer Name:- Aryan Tambe</string>
    <string name="Spicestime">Date :-22/05/2024, Time:- 6:00 PM,\n Duration:- 1 week, Trainer Name:- Aryan Tambe</string>
    <string name="Palmtime">Date :- 23/05/2024, Time:-5:00 PM,\n Duration:- 1 week, Trainer Name:- Aryan Tambe</string>
    <string name="Perfumetime">Date :- 4/05/2024, Time:-4:00 PM,\n Duration:- 2 week, Trainer Name:- Pratik Maske</string>
    <string name="Chocotime">Date :- 26/05/2024, Time:-2:00 PM,\n Duration:- 1 week, Trainer Name:- Pratik Maske</string>




</resources>

